Dunya Ramicova Costume Design Collection MSS.004
University of California, Merced Library
- Production Materials, Ephemera, and Process Notes, 66 Boxes
  - Box 83
    - As You Like It - Notes from Collaborative Meetings with Director Mark Lamos (Box 83, Folder 1)
    - As You Like It - Costume Designs by Mark Lamos (Box 83, Folder 2)
    - As You Like It - Production Correspondence (Box 83, Folder 3)
    - As You Like It - Annotated Play Script (Box 83, Folder 4)
    - As You Like It - Essay on As You Like It by Marjorie Garber, Professor of English at Harvard University (Box 83, Folder 5)
    - As You Like It - Written Research (Box 83, Folder 6)
    - As You Like It - Doubling List (Box 83, Folder 7)
    - As You Like It - Production Contact Sheet (Box 83, Folder 8)
    - As You Like It - Production Casting Additions (Box 83, Folder 9)
    - As You Like It - Costume Production Reference: Production "to do" Lists (Box 83, Folder 10)
    - As You Like It - Costume Production Reference: Costume Plots (Box 83, Folder 11)
    - As You Like It - Costume Production Reference: Costume Plots (Box 83, Folder 12)
    - As You Like It - Costume Production Reference: Costume Plots (Box 83, Folder 13)
    - As You Like It - Playbill (Box 83, Folder 14)
    - As You Like It - Reviews (Box 83, Folder 15)
    - Love's Labor's Lost - Notes from Collaborative Meetings with Director Mladen Kiselov (Box 83, Folder 16)
    - Love's Labor's Lost - Costume Production Reference (Box 83, Folder 17)
    - Love's Labor's Lost - Reviews (Box 83, Folder 18)
  - Box 84
    - Hedda Gabler - Notes from Collaborative Meetings with Director Daniel Sullivan (Box 84, Folder 1)
    - Hedda Gabler - Comparisons of English Translations of Hedda Gabler (Box 84, Folder 2)
    - Hedda Gabler - Written Research (Box 84, Folder 3)
    - Hedda Gabler - Production Correspondence (Box 84, Folder 4)
    - Hedda Gabler - Production Cast List (Box 84, Folder 5)
    - Hedda Gabler - Photograph of Annette Benning (Box 84, Folder 6)
    - Hedda Gabler - Visual Research (Box 84, Folder 7)
    - Hedda Gabler - Visual Research (Box 84, Folder 8)
    - Hedda Gabler - Preliminary Written Color Plot (Box 84, Folder 9)
    - Hedda Gabler - Costume Production Reference: Color Plot (Box 84, Folder 10)
    - Hedda Gabler - Costume Production Reference: Costume Budget (Box 84, Folder 11)
    - Hedda Gabler - Rehearsal Reports (Box 84, Folder 12)
    - Hedda Gabler - Playbill (Box 84, Folder 13)
    - Hedda Gabler - Reviews (Box 84, Folder 14)
    - Hedda Gabler - Theater Alliance League, Theater LA Ovation Best Costume Design - Larger Theater Nomination Letter and Certificate (Box 84, Folder 15)
  - Box 85
    - The Fairy Queen - Notes from Collaborative Meetings with Director David Pountney (Box 85, Folder 1)
    - The Fairy Queen - Notes on Libretto (Box 85, Folder 2)
    - The Fairy Queen - Production Correspondence (Box 85, Folder 3)
    - The Fairy Queen - Production Cast (Box 85, Folder 4)
    - The Fairy Queen - Preliminary Costume Plot (Box 85, Folder 5)
    - The Fairy Queen - Preliminary Written Color Plot (Box 85, Folder 6)
    - The Fairy Queen - Visual Research (Box 85, Folder 7)
    - The Fairy Queen - List of Designs with Number Assignments (Box 85, Folder 8)
    - The Fairy Queen - Costume Production Reference: Description of all Costumes with Revisions and Updates (Box 85, Folder 9)
    - The Fairy Queen - Costume Production Reference: Costume and Wig Budget (Box 85, Folder 10)
    - The Fairy Queen - Costume Production Reference: List of Rehearsal Clothing (Box 85, Folder 11)
  - Box 86
    - The Fairy Queen - Costume Production Reference: Principles, Chorus, Dancers, and Supernumeraries: Copies of Designs, Costume Lists, and Fabric Swatches (Box 86, Folder 1)
    - The Fairy Queen - Costume Production Reference: Principles, Chorus, Dancers, and Supernumeraries: Copies of Designs, Costume Lists, and Fabric Swatches (Box 86, Folder 2)
    - The Fairy Queen - Costume Production Reference: Principles, Chorus, Dancers, and Supernumeraries: Copies of Designs, Costume Lists, and Fabric Swatches (Box 86, Folder 3)
    - The Fairy Queen - Costume Production Reference: Principles, Chorus, Dancers, and Supernumeraries: Copies of Designs, Costume Lists, and Fabric Swatches (Box 86, Folder 4)
    - The Fairy Queen - Costume Production Reference: Principles, Chorus, Dancers, and Supernumeraries: Copies of Designs, Costume Lists, and Fabric Swatches (Box 86, Folder 5)
    - The Fairy Queen - Playbill (Box 86, Folder 6)
    - The Fairy Queen - Reviews (Box 86, Folder 7)
  - Box 87
    - Major Barbara - Notes from Collaborative Meetings with Director Lloyd Richards (Box 87, Folder 1)
    - Major Barbara - Production Contact Sheet (Box 87, Folder 2)
    - Major Barbara - Visual Research (Box 87, Folder 3)
    - Major Barbara - Costume Production Reference: Costume Plot (Box 87, Folder 4)
    - Major Barbara - Costume Production Reference: Costume Lists (Box 87, Folder 5)
    - Major Barbara - Playbill (Box 87, Folder 6)
    - Major Barbara - Reviews (Box 87, Folder 7)
    - Marriage - Notes from Collaborative Meetings with Director Andrei Belgrader (Box 87, Folder 8)
    - Marriage - Visual Research (Box 87, Folder 9)
    - Marriage - Playbill (Box 87, Folder 10)
    - Marriage - Reviews (Box 87, Folder 11)
    - The Recruiting Officer - Production Contact Sheet (Box 87, Folder 12)
    - The Recruiting Officer - Scene/Character Breakdown (Box 87, Folder 13)
    - The Recruiting Officer - Visual Research (Box 87, Folder 14)
    - The Recruiting Officer - Costume Production Reference: Costume Lists and Fabric Swatches (Box 87, Folder 15)
    - The Recruiting Officer - Playbill (Box 87, Folder 16)
    - The Recruiting Officer - Review (Box 87, Folder 17)
  - Box 88
    - An Attempt at Flying - Notes from Collaborative Meetings with Director Mladen Kiselov (Box 88, Folder 1)
    - An Attempt at Flying - Information on Playwright of An Attempt at Flying, Iordan Radichkov (Box 88, Folder 2)
    - An Attempt at Flying - Costume Production Reference: Budget (Box 88, Folder 3)
    - An Attempt at Flying - Costume Production Reference: Costume Lists, Fabric Swatches, Technical Drawings, and Research (Box 88, Folder 4)
    - An Attempt at Flying - Playbill (Box 88, Folder 5)
    - An Attempt at Flying - Review (Box 88, Folder 6)
    - Barbarians - Notes from Collaborative Meetings with Director David Jones (Box 88, Folder 7)
    - Barbarians - Costume Production Reference: Costume Lists (Box 88, Folder 8)
    - Barbarians - Pre-production Publicity (Box 88, Folder 9)
    - Barbarians - Playbill (Box 88, Folder 10)
    - Barbarians - Reviews (Box 88, Folder 11)
    - Landscape of the Body - Notes from Collaborative Meetings with Director Robert Falls (Box 88, Folder 12)
    - Landscape of the Body - Production Correspondence (Box 88, Folder 13)
    - Landscape of the Body - Production Contact Sheet (Box 88, Folder 14)
    - Landscape of the Body - Pre-production Publicity (Box 88, Folder 15)
    - Landscape of the Body - Playbill (Box 88, Folder 16)
    - Landscape of the Body - Reviews (Box 88, Folder 17)
  - Box 89
    - Aida - Notes from Collaborative Meetings with Director David Pountney (Box 89, Folder 1)
    - Aida - Production Correspondence (Box 89, Folder 2)
    - Aida - Written Research (Box 89, Folder 3)
    - Aida - Written Color Plot (Box 89, Folder 4)
    - Aida - Written Costume Description (Box 89, Folder 5)
    - Aida - Costume Production Reference: Costume Plot (Box 89, Folder 6)
    - Aida - Costume Production Reference: Costume Lists (Box 89, Folder 7)
    - Aida - Playbills (Box 89, Folder 8)
    - Aida - Playbills (Box 89, Folder 9)
  - Box 90
    - Alcina - Notes from Collaborative Meetings with Director Stephen Wadsworth - Opera Theatre of Saint Louis (Box 90, Folder 1)
    - Alcina - Production Contact Sheet - Opera Theatre of Saint Louis (Box 90, Folder 2)
    - Alcina - Opera Theatre of Saint Louis Production Schedule (Box 90, Folder 3)
    - Alcina - Production Correspondence - Opera Theatre of Saint Louis (Box 90, Folder 4)
    - Alcina - Written Color Plot - Opera Theatre of Saint Louis (Box 90, Folder 5)
    - Alcina - Costume Production Reference - Opera Theatre of Saint Louis: Costume Lists (Box 90, Folder 6)
    - Alcina - Playbill - Opera Theatre of Saint Louis (Box 90, Folder 7)
    - Alcina - Reviews Opera Theatre of Saint Louis (Box 90, Folder 8)
    - Alcina - Notes from Collaborative Meetings with Director Stephen Wadsworth – Royal Opera House (Box 90, Folder 9)
    - Alcina - Production Schedule and Cast List – Royal Opera House (Box 90, Folder 10)
    - Alcina - Production Correspondence (Box 90, Folder 11)
    - Alcina - Costume Production Reference – Royal Opera House: Copies of Designs, Costume Lists, and Fabric Swatches (Box 90, Folder 12)
    - Alcina - Pre-production Publicity – Royal Opera House (Box 90, Folder 13)
    - Alcina - Playbill – Royal Opera House (Box 90, Folder 14)
    - Alcina - Reviews – Royal Opera House (Box 90, Folder 15)
    - Melons - Notes from Collaborative Meetings with Director Gitta Honegger (Box 90, Folder 16)
    - Melons - Production Cast List (Box 90, Folder 17)
    - Melons - Production Correspondence (Box 90, Folder 18)
    - Melons - Visual Research (Box 90, Folder 19)
    - Melons - Costume Production Reference: Costume Lists and Fabric Swatches (Box 90, Folder 20)
    - Melons - Playbill (Box 90, Folder 21)
    - Melons - Reviews (Box 90, Folder 22)
    - The Winter Dancers - Notes from Collaborative Meetings with Director Keith Hack (Box 90, Folder 23)
    - The Winter Dancers - Production Cast List and Contact List (Box 90, Folder 24)
    - The Winter Dancers - Production Correspondence (Box 90, Folder 25)
    - The Winter Dancers - Written Research Notes on Native American Costume (Box 90, Folder 26)
    - The Winter Dancers - Costume Production Reference: Costume Lists (Box 90, Folder 27)
    - The Winter Dancers - Playbill (Box 90, Folder 28)
    - The Winter Dancers - American Indian Community House Inc. Press Release (Box 90, Folder 29)
  - Box 91
    - Heartbreak House - Notes from Collaborative Meetings with Director Alvin Epstein (Box 91, Folder 1)
    - Heartbreak House - Production Contact Sheet (Box 91, Folder 2)
    - Heartbreak House - Visual Research (Box 91, Folder 3)
    - Heartbreak House - Written Color Plot (Box 91, Folder 4)
    - Heartbreak House - Pre-production Publicity (Box 91, Folder 5)
    - Heartbreak House - Playbill (Box 91, Folder 6)
    - Idiot's Delight - Costume Production Reference (Box 91, Folder 8)
    - Idiot's Delight - Playbill (Box 91, Folder 9)
    - Tartuffe - Notes from Collaborative Meetings with Director Walt Jones (Box 91, Folder 10)
    - Tartuffe - Production Correspondence – Alaska Repertory Theatre (Box 91, Folder 11)
    - Tartuffe - Playbill - Alaska Repertory Theatre (Box 91, Folder 12)
    - Tartuffe - Review - Alaska Repertory Theatre (Box 91, Folder 13)
    - Tartuffe - Production Cast List and Contact Sheet – Yale Repertory Theatre (Box 91, Folder 14)
    - Tartuffe - Costume Production Reference - Yale Repertory Theatre: Budget (Box 91, Folder 15)
    - Tartuffe - Costume Production Reference - Yale Repertory Theatre: Copies of Designs, Costume Lists, and Fabric Swatches (Box 91, Folder 16)
    - Tartuffe - Playbill - Yale Repertory Theatre (Box 91, Folder 17)
    - Tartuffe - Reviews - Yale Repertory Theatre (Box 91, Folder 18)
  - Box 92
    - Emmeline - Notes from Collaborative Meetings with Director Francesca Zambello (Box 92, Folder 1)
    - Emmeline - Written Research (Box 92, Folder 2)
    - Emmeline - Preliminary Costume Plot (Box 92, Folder 3)
    - Emmeline - Visual Research (Box 92, Folder 4)
    - Emmeline - Costume Production Reference: Written Color Plot (Box 92, Folder 5)
    - Emmeline - Costume Production Reference: Costume Lists for all principles, chorus and supernumeraries (Box 92, Folder 6)
    - Emmeline - Costume Production Reference: Copies of all designs (Box 92, Folder 7)
    - Emmeline - Pre-production Publicity for PBS Broadcast of Emmeline on April 2, 1997 (Box 92, Folder 8)
    - Emmeline - Pre-production Publicity for New York City Opera Performances in March and April, 1998 (Box 92, Folder 9)
    - Emmeline - Playbill – Santa Fe Opera – Premiered July 27, 1996 (Box 92, Folder 10)
    - Emmeline - Reviews for Santa Fe Opera Performances (Box 92, Folder 11)
    - Emmeline - Playbill New York City Opera – Premiered March 31, 1998 (Box 92, Folder 12)
    - Emmeline - Reviews for New York City Opera Performances (Box 92, Folder 13)
    - Jenufa - Notes from Collaborative Meetings with Stephen Wadsworth (Box 92, Folder 14)
    - Jenufa - Production Casting and Schedule (Box 92, Folder 15)
    - Jenufa - Preliminary Costume Plot and Scene Breakdown (Box 92, Folder 16)
    - Jenufa - Visual Research (Box 92, Folder 17)
    - Jenufa - Costume Production Reference (Box 92, Folder 18)
    - Jenufa - Playbill (Box 92, Folder 19)
  - Box 93
    - Bloody Poetry - Notes from Collaborative Meetings with Director Lynne Meadow (Box 93, Folder 1)
    - Bloody Poetry - Production Contact Sheet and Cast List (Box 93, Folder 2)
    - Bloody Poetry - Production Correspondence (Box 93, Folder 3)
    - Bloody Poetry - Scene Designs by John Lee Beatty (Box 93, Folder 4)
    - Bloody Poetry - Costume Production Reference: Costume Lists (Box 93, Folder 5)
    - Bloody Poetry - Playbill (Box 93, Folder 6)
    - Serious Money - Notes from Collaborative Meetings with Directors Anthony Taccone and Sharon Ott (Box 93, Folder 7)
    - Serious Money - Production Cast List and Contact List (Box 93, Folder 8)
    - Serious Money - Production Dramaturgy Notes (Box 93, Folder 9)
    - Serious Money - Scene Breakdown by Actor (Box 93, Folder 10)
    - Serious Money - Prop List (Box 93, Folder 11)
    - Serious Money - Visual Research (Box 93, Folder 12)
    - Serious Money - Costume Production Reference: Preliminary Costume Lists (Box 93, Folder 13)
    - Serious Money - Costume Production Reference: Final Costume Lists (Box 93, Folder 14)
    - Serious Money - Playbill (Box 93, Folder 15)
    - Serious Money - Reviews (Box 93, Folder 16)
    - The Man Who Could See Through Time - Playbill (Box 93, Folder 17)
    - The Man Who Could See Through Time - Reviews (Box 93, Folder 18)
    - A Winterfest I - Production Schedule (Box 93, Folder 19)
    - A Winterfest I - Production Planning (Box 93, Folder 20)
    - A Winterfest I - Production Meeting Notes (Box 93, Folder 21)
    - A Winterfest I - Notes from Collaborative Meetings with Director Barnet Kellman (Box 93, Folder 22)
    - A Winterfest I - Costume Plot (Box 93, Folder 23)
    - A Winterfest I - Notes from Collaborative Meetings with Director Dana B. Westberg (Box 93, Folder 24)
    - A Winterfest I - Costume Plot (Box 93, Folder 25)
    - A Winterfest I - Notes from Collaborative Meetings with Director Robert Allan Ackerman (Box 93, Folder 26)
    - A Winterfest I - Costume Plot (Box 93, Folder 27)
    - A Winterfest I - Notes from Collaborative Meetings with Director James A. Simpson (Box 93, Folder 28)
    - A Winterfest I - Playbill (Box 93, Folder 29)
  - Box 94
    - Fools - Notes from Collaborative Meetings with Director Walton Jones (Box 94, Folder 1)
    - Fools - Production Correspondence (Box 94, Folder 2)
    - Fools - Costume Production Reference: Costume Plot (Box 94, Folder 3)
    - Fools - Costume Production Reference: Wig and Facial Hair Designs (by DR) (Box 94, Folder 4)
    - Fools - Costume Production Reference: Costume Lists (Box 94, Folder 5)
    - Fools - Pre-production Publicity (Box 94, Folder 6)
    - Fools - Playbill (Box 94, Folder 7)
    - The Devil's Disciple - Notes from Collaborative Meetings with Director Stan Wojewodski (Box 94, Folder 8)
    - The Devil's Disciple - Written Research (Box 94, Folder 9)
    - The Devil's Disciple - Costume Production Reference (Box 94, Folder 10)
    - The Father - Notes from Collaborative Meetings with Director Robert Brustein (Box 94, Folder 11)
    - The Father - Production Correspondence (Box 94, Folder 12)
    - The Father - Costume Production Reference: Costume Plot (Box 94, Folder 13)
    - The Father - Costume Production Reference: Costume Lists (Box 94, Folder 14)
    - The Father - Playbill (Box 94, Folder 15)
    - The Pretenders - Notes from Collaborative Meetings with Director Alvin Epstein (Box 94, Folder 16)
    - The Pretenders - Production Cast List (Box 94, Folder 17)
    - The Pretenders - A Brief History of Norway (Box 94, Folder 18)
    - The Pretenders - Costume Production Reference: Costume Lists (Box 94, Folder 19)
    - The Pretenders - Playbill (Box 94, Folder 20)
    - The Pretenders - Review (Box 94, Folder 21)
    - La Ronde - Notes from Collaborative Meetings with Director David Trainer (Box 94, Folder 22)
    - La Ronde - Costume Production Reference: Costume Lists (Box 94, Folder 23)
    - La Ronde - Playbill (Box 94, Folder 24)
    - Peer Gynt - Notes from Collaborative Meetings with Director Nikos Psacharopoulos (Box 94, Folder 25)
    - Peer Gynt - Playbill (Box 94, Folder 26)
  - Box 95
    - Man is Man - Production Correspondence (Box 95, Folder 1)
    - Man is Man - Production Contact Sheet (Box 95, Folder 2)
    - The Misanthrope - Notes from Collaborative Meetings with Director Mark Lamos (Box 95, Folder 3)
    - The Misanthrope - Written Research (Box 95, Folder 4)
    - The Misanthrope - Costume Production Reference: Costume Lists (Box 95, Folder 5)
    - The Misanthrope - Pre-production Publicity (Box 95, Folder 6)
    - The Misanthrope - Playbill (Box 95, Folder 7)
    - Uncle Vanya - Notes from Collaborative Meetings with Director Lloyd Richards (Box 95, Folder 8)
    - Uncle Vanya - Annotated Script of Uncle Vanya (Box 95, Folder 9)
    - Uncle Vanya - Costume Production Reference: Costume Budgets (Box 95, Folder 10)
    - Uncle Vanya - Costume Production Reference: Costume Lists (Box 95, Folder 11)
    - Uncle Vanya - Playbill (Box 95, Folder 12)
    - Uncle Vanya - Reviews (Box 95, Folder 13)
    - Elizabeth I - Notes from Collaborative Meetings with Director Liviu Ciulei (Box 95, Folder 14)
    - Elizabeth I - Production Cast List (Box 95, Folder 15)
    - Elizabeth I - Scene Breakdown (Box 95, Folder 16)
    - Elizabeth I - Costume Production Reference: Costume Lists (Box 95, Folder 17)
    - Elizabeth I - Reviews (Box 95, Folder 18)
    - The Dreamer Examines His Pillow, A Heterosexual Homily - Notes from Collaborative Meetings with Director June Stein (Box 95, Folder 19)
    - The Dreamer Examines His Pillow, A Heterosexual Homily - Production Correspondence (Box 95, Folder 20)
    - The Dreamer Examines His Pillow, A Heterosexual Homily - Playbill (Box 95, Folder 21)
  - Box 96
    - Children of the Sun - Notes from Collaborative Meetings with Director Nikos Psacharopoulos (Box 96, Folder 1)
    - Children of the Sun - Costume Production Reference: Costume Plot (Box 96, Folder 2)
    - Children of the Sun - Costume Production Reference: Costume Lists (Box 96, Folder 3)
    - Children of the Sun - Playbill (Box 96, Folder 4)
    - Children of the Sun - Review (Box 96, Folder 5)
    - Three Sisters - Manhattan Theatre Club - Notes from Collaborative Meetings with Director Lynne Meadow (Box 96, Folder 6)
    - Three Sisters - Manhattan Theatre Club - Scene Design (Box 96, Folder 7)
    - Three Sisters - Manhattan Theatre Club - Costume Production Reference: Costume Lists (Box 96, Folder 8)
    - Three Sisters - Manhattan Theatre Club - Playbill (Box 96, Folder 9)
    - Three Sisters – Hartford Stage Company - Notes from Collaborative Meetings with Director Mark Lamos (Box 96, Folder 10)
    - Three Sisters – Hartford Stage Company - Production Contact Sheet (Box 96, Folder 11)
    - Three Sisters – Hartford Stage Company - Costume Production Reference: Costume Lists (Box 96, Folder 12)
    - Three Sisters – Hartford Stage Company - Playbill (Box 96, Folder 13)
    - Three Sisters – Hartford Stage Company - Reviews (Box 96, Folder 14)
  - Box 97
    - Ivanov - Notes from Collaborative Meetings with Director John Madden (Box 97, Folder 1)
    - Ivanov - Production Cast List (Box 97, Folder 2)
    - Ivanov - Costume Production Reference: Costume Plot (Box 97, Folder 3)
    - Ivanov - Costume Production Reference: Costume Lists (Box 97, Folder 4)
    - Ivanov - Playbill (Box 97, Folder 5)
    - Summerfolk - Costume Production Reference: Costume Inventory Lists for All Characters (Box 97, Folder 6)
    - Summerfolk - Playbill (Box 97, Folder 7)
    - Summerfolk - Review (Box 97, Folder 8)
    - Platonov - Notes from Collaborative Meeting with Director Nikos Psacharopoulos (Box 97, Folder 9)
    - Platonov - Production Correspondence (Box 97, Folder 10)
    - Platonov - Playbill (Box 97, Folder 11)
    - Platonov - Review (Box 97, Folder 12)
  - Box 98
    - A Doll House - Notes from Collaborative Meetings with Director Emily Mann (Box 98, Folder 1)
    - A Doll House - Visual Research (Box 98, Folder 2)
    - A Doll House - Costume Production Reference: Fabric Swatches for Nora's Italian Costume (Box 98, Folder 3)
    - A Doll House - Playbill (Box 98, Folder 4)
    - A Doll House - Reviews (Box 98, Folder 5)
    - A Doll House - Written Research on Henrik Ibsen (Box 98, Folder 6)
    - A Doll House - Written Research on 19th Century Clothing (1870s) (Box 98, Folder 7)
    - A Doll House - Costume Production Reference: Costume Lists and Fabric Swatches (Box 98, Folder 8)
    - A Doll House - Costume Production Reference: Lists: Accessories, Fabric, and Trim (Box 98, Folder 9)
    - A Doll House - Playbill (Box 98, Folder 10)
    - A Doll House - Reviews (Box 98, Folder 11)
    - La Traviata - Notes from Collaborative Meetings with Director Andrei Serban (Box 98, Folder 12)
    - La Traviata - Costume Production Reference: Costume Lists and Fabric Swatches (Box 98, Folder 13)
    - La Traviata - Playbill (Box 98, Folder 14)
    - La Traviata - Review (Box 98, Folder 15)
    - The Tempest - Notes from Collaborative Meetings with Director Mark Lamos (Box 98, Folder 16)
    - The Tempest - Narrative of Technical Aspects of the Production (Box 98, Folder 17)
    - The Tempest - Scene Breakdown by Character (Box 98, Folder 18)
    - The Tempest - Costume Production Reference: Costume Plot (Box 98, Folder 19)
    - The Tempest - Playbill (Box 98, Folder 20)
    - The Tempest - Review (Box 98, Folder 21)
    - Laughing Stock - Production Correspondence (Box 98, Folder 22)
    - Laughing Stock - Production cast List and Contact Sheet (Box 98, Folder 23)
    - Laughing Stock - Production Scene Design (Box 98, Folder 24)
    - Laughing Stock - Costume Production Reference: Costume Lists for All Three Plays (Box 98, Folder 25)
    - Laughing Stock - Playbill (Box 98, Folder 26)
    - Laughing Stock - Reviews (Box 98, Folder 27)
  - Box 99
    - Windows - Production Notebook (Box 99, Folder 1)
    - Windows - Notes from Collaborative Meetings with Director Robert Egan (Box 99, Folder 2)
    - Windows - Production Contact List (Box 99, Folder 3)
    - Windows - Scene Design (Box 99, Folder 4)
    - Windows - Scene Breakdown (Box 99, Folder 5)
    - Windows - Visual Research (Box 99, Folder 6)
    - Windows - Costume Production Reference: Fabric Swatches and Costume Lists (Box 99, Folder 7)
    - Windows - Pre-production Publicity (Box 99, Folder 8)
    - Windows - Playbill (Box 99, Folder 9)
    - Ajax - Playbill (Box 99, Folder 10)
    - Ajax - Reviews (Box 99, Folder 11)
  - Box 100
    - The Electrification of the Soviet Union - Notes from Collaborative Meetings with Director Peter Sellars (Box 100, Folder 1)
    - The Electrification of the Soviet Union - Libretto (Box 100, Folder 2)
    - The Electrification of the Soviet Union - Costume Production Reference: Costume Lists (Box 100, Folder 3)